Authors	Title	Publication	Volume	Number	Pages	Year	Publisher	Authors			
"Aare, Cecilia; "	A Narratological Approach to Literary Journalism: How an Interplay between Voice and Point of View May Create Empathy with the Other.	Literary Journalism Studies	8	1		2016		Aare	 Cecilia; 		
"Alexander, Robert; "	"“My story is always escaping into other people”: Subjectivity, objectivity, and the double in American literary journalism"	Literary Journalism Studies	1	1	57-66	2009		Alexander	 Robert; 		
"Alexander, Robert; "	“The Right Kind of Eyes”: Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas as a Novel of Journalistic Development	Literary Journalism Studies	4	1	19-36	2012		Alexander	 Robert; 		
"Armao, Rosemary; "	The Rainy Season: Three Lives in the New South Africa					2016	"INT ASSOC LITERARY JOURNALISM STUDIES MEDILL SCHOOL OF JOURNALISM, NORTHWESTERN UNIV, 1845 SHERIDAN RD, EVANSTON, IL 60208 USA"	Armao	 Rosemary; 		
"Bowe, Brian J; "	A Brain Full of Contraband: The Islamic Gonzo Writing of Michael Muhammad Knight	Literary Journalism Studies	4	1		2012		Bowe	 Brian J; 		
"Boynton, Robert; "	Notes toward a Supreme Nonfiction: Teaching Literary Reportage in the Twenty-first Century	Literary Journalism Studies	5	2	125-131	2013		Boynton	 Robert; 		
"Calvi, Pablo; "	Latin America’s Own “New Journalism”	Literary Journalism Studies	2	2	63-86	2010		Calvi	 Pablo; 		
"Calvi, Pablo; "	Leila Guerriero and the Uncertain Narrator.	Literary Journalism Studies	7	1		2015		Calvi	 Pablo; 		
"Cowling, Lesley; "	Echoes of an African Drum: The Lost Literary Journalism of 1950s South Africa.	Literary Journalism Studies	8	1		2016		Cowling	 Lesley; 		
"Cumming, Doug; "	‘Just as I Am’? Marshall Frady’s Making of Billy Graham	Literary Journalism Studies	6	2		2014		Cumming	 Doug; 		
"Dow, William; "	Unreading Modernism: Richard Wright's Literary Journalism.	Literary Journalism Studies	5	2		2013		Dow	 William; 		
"Dow, William; "	"Writing Dark Times: Settings, Immersions in Agnes Smedley and Meridel Le Sueur"	Literary Journalism in an International Context. The 2nd International Conference for Literary Journalism Studies			18-19	2007		Dow	 William; 		
"Dowling, David; "	"Beyond the Program Era: Tracy Kidder, John D'Agata, and the Rise of Literary Journalism at the Iowa Writers' Workshop."	Literary Journalism Studies	8	1		2016		Dowling	 David; 		
"González, Juan Orlando; "	Revolution is Such a Beautiful Word! Literary Journalism in Castro’s Cuba	Literary Journalism Studies			28-Sep	2012		González	 Juan Orlando; 		
"Gooch, Cheryl Renee; "	The Literary Mind of a Cornfield Journalist: Joel Chandler Harris’s 1904 Negro Question Articles	Literary Journalism Studies			79			Gooch	 Cheryl Renee; 		
"Gorbach, Julien; "	Ben Hecht: The Old New Journalist.	Literary Journalism Studies	7	2		2015		Gorbach	 Julien; 		
"Harbers, Frank; "	Between fact and fiction: Arnon Grunberg on his literary journalism	Literary Journalism Studies	2	1	74-84	2010		Harbers	 Frank; 		
"Hartsock, John C; "	The Literature in the Journalism of Nobel Prize Winner Svetlana Alexievich.	Literary Journalism Studies	7	2		2015		Hartsock	 John C; 		
"Horodecka, Magdalena; "	The Hermeneutic Relation between Reporter and Ancient Historian in Ryszard Kapuściński's Travels with Herodotus.	Literary Journalism Studies	7	2		2015		Horodecka	 Magdalena; 		
"Hudson, Berkley; Townsend, Rebecca; "	"Unraveling the webs of intimacy and influence: Willie Morris and Harper’s Magazine, 1967–1971"	Literary Journalism Studies	1	2	63-78	2009		Hudson	 Berkley; Townsend	 Rebecca; 	
"Isager, Christine; "	"Playful Imitation at Work: The Formation of a Danish"" Gonzo Thingummy""."	Literary Journalism Studies	8	1		2016		Isager	 Christine; 		
"Jacobs, Michael; "	Confronting the (Un) Reality of Pranksterdom: Tom Wolfe and The Electric Kool-Aid Acid Test.	Literary Journalism Studies	7	2		2015		Jacobs	 Michael; 		
"Joseph, Sue; "	"Preferring"" Dirty"" to"" Literary"" Journalism: In Australia, Margaret Simons Challenges the Jargon While Producing the Texts."	Literary Journalism Studies	7	1		2015		Joseph	 Sue; 		
"Josephi, Beate; Müller, Christine; "	Differently drawn boundaries of the permissible in German and Australian literary journalism	Literary Journalism Studies	1	1	67-78	2009		Josephi	 Beate; Müller	 Christine; 	
"Keeble, Richard Lance; "	Literary Journalism and the Aesthetics of Experience					2016	"INT ASSOC LITERARY JOURNALISM STUDIES MEDILL SCHOOL OF JOURNALISM, NORTHWESTERN UNIV, 1845 SHERIDAN RD, EVANSTON, IL 60208 USA"	Keeble	 Richard Lance; 		
"Keeble, Richard; "	War and the journalistic imagination: The reporting of George Orwell and Robert Fisk	Literary Journalism: Newsletter of the International Association of Literary Journalism Studies			8-Apr	2009		Keeble	 Richard; 		
"Larssen, Kristiane; Hornmoen, Harald; "	The Literary Journalist as Fellow Human Being	Literary Journalism Studies	5	1	81-94			Larssen	 Kristiane; Hornmoen	 Harald; 	
"Little, Janine; "	Teaching literary journalism at a newspaper	Literary journalism	4	3	22-22	2010	International Association for Literary Journalism Studies	Little	 Janine; 		
"MacNamara, Donald; "	Myles of Writing: Brian O’Nolan’s Newspaper Columns	Literary Journalism Studies	4		29-44	2012		MacNamara	 Donald; 		
"Maguire, Miles; "	Richard Critchfield:“Genius” Journalism and the Fallacy of Verification	Literary Journalism Studies	1	2	21-Sep	2009		Maguire	 Miles; 		
"Maguire, Miles; "	Literary Journalism on the Air: What David Isay's Travels in the Footsteps of Joseph Mitchell Can Tell Us about the Nature of Multimedia.	Literary Journalism Studies	6	1		2014		Maguire	 Miles; 		
"Maguire, Miles; "	Recent Trends and Topics in Literary Journalism Scholarship	LITERARY JOURNALISM STUDIES	8	1	140-151	2016	"INT ASSOC LITERARY JOURNALISM STUDIES MEDILL SCHOOL OF JOURNALISM, NORTHWESTERN UNIV, 1845 SHERIDAN RD, EVANSTON, IL 60208 USA"	Maguire	 Miles; 		
"Maguire, Roberta S; "	From Fiction to Fact: Zora Neale Hurston and the Ruby McCollum Trial.	Literary Journalism Studies	7	1		2015		Maguire	 Roberta S; 		
"McDonald, Willa; "	A Vagabond: The Literary Journalism of John Stanley James.	Literary Journalism Studies	6	1		2014		McDonald	 Willa; 		
"McQueen, Kate; "	"Into the Courtroom: Paul"" Sling"" Schlesinger and the Origins of German Literary Trial Reportage."	Literary Journalism Studies	7	2		2015		McQueen	 Kate; 		
"McQueen, Kate; "	One of Us: The Story of Anders Breivik and the Massacre in Norway					2016	"INT ASSOC LITERARY JOURNALISM STUDIES MEDILL SCHOOL OF JOURNALISM, NORTHWESTERN UNIV, 1845 SHERIDAN RD, EVANSTON, IL 60208 USA"	McQueen	 Kate; 		
"Meuret, Isabelle; "	"Journalism as An Aesthetic, revue critique de Aesthetic Journalism: How to inform Without Informing, by Alfredo Cramerotti"	Literary journalism studies	2	1	117-119	2010		Meuret	 Isabelle; 		
"Meuret, Isabelle; "	"In Their Own Voices Celebrating Brothers: Black and Poor-A True Story of Courage and Survival, 25 Years Later."	Literary Journalism Studies	5	2		2013		Meuret	 Isabelle; 		
"Meuret, Isabelle; "	Rebels with a Cause: Women Reporting the Spanish Civil War.	Literary Journalism Studies	7	1		2015		Meuret	 Isabelle; 		
"Mosser, Jason; "	What’s gonzo about Gonzo Journalism?	Literary Journalism Studies	4	1	85-90	2012		Mosser	 Jason; 		
"Mulgrew, Nick; "	Tracing the Seam: Narrative Journalism and Imaginings in South African Literature.	Literary Journalism Studies	6	1		2014		Mulgrew	 Nick; 		
"Nandorfy, Martha; "	Charles Bowden's Anarcho-Biotic Poetics.	Literary Journalism Studies	6	2		2014		Nandorfy	 Martha; 		
"Nelson, Ashlee; "	Gonzo Text: Disentangling Meaning in Hunter S. Thompson's Journalism					2016	"INT ASSOC LITERARY JOURNALISM STUDIES MEDILL SCHOOL OF JOURNALISM, NORTHWESTERN UNIV, 1845 SHERIDAN RD, EVANSTON, IL 60208 USA"	Nelson	 Ashlee; 		
"Nuttall, Nick; "	Apocalypse and Hell: Hunter's Thompson's American Dream	Literary Journalism Studies	4	1	113	2012		Nuttall	 Nick; 		
"Passos, Mateus Yuri Ribeiro da Silva; Nering, Érica Masiero; Carvalho, Juliano Maurício de; "	The chudnovsky case: how literary journalism can open the black box of science	Literary Journalism Studies			27-45	2010		Passos	 Mateus Yuri Ribeiro da Silva; Nering	 Érica Masiero; Carvalho	 Juliano Maurício de; 
"Pauly, John J; "	Literary journalism and the drama of civic life	Literary Journalism Studies				2011	International Association for Literary Journalism Studies	Pauly	 John J; 		
"Poerksen, Bernhard; "	The Milieu of a Magazine: Tempo as an Exponent German New Journalism						LJS: Literary Journalism Studies	Poerksen	 Bernhard; 		
"Reynolds, Bill; "	On the Road to Gonzo: Hunter S. Thompson's Early Literary Journalism (1961-1970)	Literary Journalism Studies	4	1	51-84	2012		Reynolds	 Bill; 		
"Reynolds, Bill; "	An Interview with John Vaillant					2016	"INT ASSOC LITERARY JOURNALISM STUDIES MEDILL SCHOOL OF JOURNALISM, NORTHWESTERN UNIV, 1845 SHERIDAN RD, EVANSTON, IL 60208 USA"	Reynolds	 Bill; 		
"Roberts, Nancy L; "	Firing the Canon: The Historical Search for Literary Journalism’s Missing Links	Literary Journalism Studies	4		81-93	2012		Roberts	 Nancy L; 		
"Roberts, Nancy L; "	"Meridel Le Sueur, Dorothy Day, and the Literary Journalism of Advocacy During the Great Depression."	Literary Journalism Studies	7	1		2015		Roberts	 Nancy L; 		
"Roberts, William; Giles, Fiona; "	Mapping nonfiction narrative: a new theoretical approach to analyzing literary journalism	Literary Journalism Studies	6	2	101-117	2014		Roberts	 William; Giles	 Fiona; 	
"Roessner, Amber; "	The Routledge Handbook of Magazine Research: The Future of the Magazine Form					2016	"INT ASSOC LITERARY JOURNALISM STUDIES MEDILL SCHOOL OF JOURNALISM, NORTHWESTERN UNIV, 1845 SHERIDAN RD, EVANSTON, IL 60208 USA"	Roessner	 Amber; 		
"Rogers, James Silas; "	Man in Profile: Joseph Mitchell of the New Yorker					2016	"INT ASSOC LITERARY JOURNALISM STUDIES MEDILL SCHOOL OF JOURNALISM, NORTHWESTERN UNIV, 1845 SHERIDAN RD, EVANSTON, IL 60208 USA"	Rogers	 James Silas; 		
"Roiland, Joshua M; "	""" Just People"" are Just People: Langston Hughes and the Populist Power of African American Literary Journalism."	Literary Journalism Studies	5	2		2013		Roiland	 Joshua M; 		
"Sabroe, Morten; "	Overreacting with Style: Danish Football According to Morten Sabroe	LITERARY JOURNALISM STUDIES	8	1	97-104	2016	"INT ASSOC LITERARY JOURNALISM STUDIES MEDILL SCHOOL OF JOURNALISM, NORTHWESTERN UNIV, 1845 SHERIDAN RD, EVANSTON, IL 60208 USA"	Sabroe	 Morten; 		
"Schreiber, Holly E; "	Journalistic Critique through Parody in Stephen Crane’s “An Experiment in Misery”	Literary Journalism Studies	6	1		2014		Schreiber	 Holly E; 		
"Sims, Norman; "	The problem and the promise of literary journalism studies	Literary Journalism Studies	1	1	16-Jul	2009		Sims	 Norman; 		
"Soares, Isabel; "	South: where travel meets literary journalism	"Literary journalism studies, Evanston"	1	1	17-30	2009		Soares	 Isabel; 		
"TRINDADE, A; "	What Will the Future Bring						LJS: Literary Journalism Studies	TRINDADE	 A; 		
"Tulloch, John; "	"Kicking the canon in the breeches: an appreciation of Professor Nancy Roberts’s keynote address,“Firing the Canon”"	Literary Journalism Studies	4	2	95-99	2012	International Association for Literary Journalism Studies	Tulloch	 John; 		
"Vaessens, Tomas; "	"Making overtures: literature and journalism, 1968 and 2011: a Dutch perspective"	Literary Journalism Studies	3	2	55-72	2011		Vaessens	 Tomas; 		
"Wilson, Christopher P; "	The Underwater Narrative: Joan Didion’s Miami	Literary Journalism Studies	3		29-Sep	2011		Wilson	 Christopher P; 		
"Wilson, Christopher P; "	Finding Emma Larkin.	Literary Journalism Studies	6	2		2014		Wilson	 Christopher P; 		